# **COURSES**

01.2020 – 10.2020 Codemy S.A. (Kodilla)

Java developer plus

# Realised projects:

- **Flights search engine** (technologies: Java 8, Spring, Hibernate, MySQL, REST API, Gradle, Git, Vaadin)
- Task REST API (technologies: Java 8, Spring, REST API, MySQL, Hibernate, Gradle, Swagger, Thymeleaf, Webdriver Selenium, Git)
- **Online shop backend** (technologies: Java 8, REST API, MySQL, Gradle, Hibernate, Postman, Git)
- Checkers game (technologies: JavaFX)

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Java 8
- SQL
- IntelliJ
- Gradle
- Spring Boot
- Git
- Hibernate
- Mockito
- Rest API
- JUnit

## **EDUCATION**

10.2011 - 02.2016	Lublin University of Technology
	Management and Production Engineering

### **EXPERIENCE**

04.2019 - now	Zakład Energetyki Cieplnej Sp. z o. o.   Ostrzeszów
	office worker
07.2018 - 01.2019	CSM Zbrojarnia Sp. z o. o.   Wrocław
	deputy production manager
02.2017 - 07.2018	Okręgowa Spółdzielnia Mleczarska   Krasnystaw
	machine operator

## **LANGUAGES**

English - Upper-Intermediate

# **STRENGHTS**

teamwork, always ready to learn new things, good communication skills

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

# KAMIL KOWALCZYK JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER



### **PERSONAL DATA**

Cell:

+48 602 148 633

E-mail:

kamilkowalczyk27@o2.pl

https://github.com/kamilkow alczyk27 LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kamil-kowalczyk-java/

### **ABOUT ME**

Engineer by education, with a passion for figure skating. For the last two years I started to devote a large part of my free time to programming. Initially I was learning by myself, using various free courses, books or YouTube. Later, on a Java bootcamp, when the initial fun pulled me so much that I decided to do it professionally. I feel the best in: Spring Boot, Hibernate, MySQL, REST API, Gradle and Git.